#### CONTACT

ADAM T'KOY

a.p.tkoy@gmail.com 630-363-0924

# COMPUTER AND DATA SCIENTIST

Constantly learning and adapting. With a firm grasp of computer science fundamentals, I quickly adjust to new programming languages and problem solving challenges. I will push my boundaries to achieve worthy goals, as evidenced in starting my education over to earn a second bachelor's degree in Statistics and Computer Science. Most of all, I love to collaborate because working with amazing people has been the highlight of all my prior career experiences.

- Programming in C, C++, Java, Javascript, OCaml, Python, and R
  - · Version control with GitHub
  - Analyzing data to produce summary findings and visualizations
  - Video editing, motion graphics and graphic design
  - Cleaned and analyzed data in Tableau during Career Experience at Apple
  - Completed courses in SQL and Swift programming via Coursera

#### **EDUCATION**

# UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS URBANA-CHAMPAIGN

Bachelor of Science, Statistics and Computer Science - 3.91 GPA

#### **DEPAUL UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor of Science, Marketing - 3.94 GPA

#### **COLLEGE OF DUPAGE**

Associate in Applied Science, Film/Video Production - 4.0 GPA

# EXPERIENCE

# **GENIUS ADMIN. 2022-2023**

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

- Resolved and escalated issues for in-store repairs
- Managed flow of repairs to and from offsite repair facility
- Maintained organization and inventory of repair room
- Collaborated across store teams to ensure excellent customer experiences

### APPLE CAREER EXPERIENCE, 2023

Apple, Inc., Cupertino, CA

Supported the Manufacturing Quality Engineering Color team for 5 months:

- Assisted with preparing reports and managing parts for reviews with Industrial Design team
- Organized limit samples and excess parts for storage or recycling
- Operated special equipment to measure color and texture

# PRODUCT SPECIALIST, 2019-2022

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

Efficiently created solutions for customers, including scheduling repair/support appointments, recommending purchases, and facilitating initial device set up

# PROGRAM SUPPORT SPECIALIST. 2017-2019

College of DuPage, Glen Ellyn, IL

- Analyzed student data to create/update statistical reports each semester
- Updated 3 internal data resource websites